[{"answer": "Well, from what I have been led to believe, as I stand here, there's no connection yet identified as to the coordination.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Is there a connection here?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "They are in a really tough neighborhood and there's a lot of uncertainty now that surrounds them.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 50, "question": "What do you make of this?", "qSentId": 49}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you that clearly I walked out of the meeting with the understanding that the Israeli government is a little frustrated with the lack of certainty on where -- on behalf of the United States.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "What happened there?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Well, I think that -- look, Prime Minister Netanyahu can reach the president any time he wants.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "What's going on here?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, here's what I'd say.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "As a strong supporter of Israel, what do you say?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, here's another thing.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "On this 11th anniversary of 9/11, where do you see the greatest threat to the United States?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "I was at a temporary command center that Governor Pataki and I had set up at the New York City Police Academy on 22nd Street.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 177, "question": "Where were you exactly on that evening at 9:00 p.m. 11 years ago today?", "qSentId": 176}, {"answer": "LITZER: Yes.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "When I look back on it?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Sure, sure.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Is that possible?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I thought they were two very interesting conventions.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "So what did you make of the Democrat's convention?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "...that would allow that to once again come into play?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Well I mean I debated Mitt maybe 11 times, 12 times in '07, going into '08.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "And Mitt Romney participated when you did it as well?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "That will be very lively and it ends up being a more important debate for Paul Ryan than it does for Joe Biden.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "That could be lively?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Every year on September 11th -- and you know it's the toughest day in the world for us.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Howard, let me ask you, how are you doing tonight?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I was standing in front of my son's nursery school or Kindergarten.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "How did you learn that a plane -- yes, a plane had crashed into the North Tower?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "You know, my sister picked up the phone and my sister, Edi, runs our relief fund.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What did he tell her?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, one of our competitors named Broker Tech was really pushing to open, because this was their big chance, you know.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Why was it so important to reopen so quickly?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I'll tell anybody -- I'm telling you.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "You think they should change that or try to change that?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "But do you worry about future terror threats in New York?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, I'm certain that we are better prepared.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Are you thinking -- are you thinking all of us are better prepared now?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "You know, I'm probably leaning -- in the presidential race toward Romney.", "docId": "120911pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "You want to tell our viewers which candidate you are leaning toward?", "qSentId": 545}]